?Are you ready kids-
？你们准​​备好了吗孩子们-
:(KIDS (VOICEOVER
.Aye, aye, Captain
:(孩子们（画外音
.是啊，是啊，船长
.I can hear you-
.我能听到你-
:(KIDS (VOICEOVER
!Aye, aye, Captain
:(孩子们（画外音
！是啊是啊，队长
!Oh-
！哦-
THEME SONG: Who lives in
?a pineapple under the sea
主题曲：谁住在
？海底的菠萝
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
Absorbent and yellow
.and porous is he
吸水性和黄色
.他是多孔的
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
If nautical nonsense
,be something you wish
如果航海废话
,成为你所希望的
,SpongeBob SquarePants
then drop on the deck
,海绵宝宝
然后落在甲板上
.and flop like a fish
.然后像鱼一样扑通扑通
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
?Ready
？准备好
,SpongeBob SquarePants
,海绵宝宝
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
[LAUGHS]
[笑]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
NARRATOR: Ah, the Krusty
Krab, Bikini Bottom's
旁白：啊，库斯蒂
蟹肉，比基尼泳裤
premiere daytime
eatery, where it
白天首映
餐馆，在那里
will be closing
.time right about
即将关闭
.时间正好
.Now, 8 o'clock-
.现在，8点钟——
.So long, suckers
.再见，傻瓜
I got a hot date with a little
.lady, and her name is clarinet
我和小小有个约会
.lady，她的名字是单簧管
?What
？什么
?Are you open-
？你开放吗-
.Read the sign-
.阅读标志-
I'll have a Krabby Patty Deluxe-
.and a double chilli kelp fries
我要一份豪华蟹肉饼-
.还有双辣椒海带薯条
.No you won't-
.不，你不会-
.I can't hang out here all night
.我不能整晚都在这里闲逛
.I've got a life
.我有自己的生活
Well, fine, if you-
.don't want my money
好吧，好吧，如果你——
.不要我的钱
?Money-
？钱-
You mean, if we
,stayed open later
你的意思是，如果我们
,稍后继续营业
?you'd give us your money
？你愿意给我们你的钱
.Sure-
。当然-
Mr. Squidward, welcome-
.to the night shift
章鱼哥先生，欢迎——
.到夜班
From now on, the Krusty
.Krab is open 24 hours a day
从现在开始，库斯提
.Krab 24小时营业
?What-
？什么-
!Yay-
！耶-
.Wow-
。哇-
Now we never have
.to stop working
现在我们从来没有
.停止工作
.Mr. Krabs-
。先生。蟹蟹-
.See you in the morning boys-
.早上见，孩子们-
.I can't hang out here all night
.我不能整晚都在这里闲逛
.I got a life
.我有一个生活
.Mr. Krabs-
。先生。蟹蟹-
,Isn't this great, Squidward-
,just you and me, together
，这不是很棒吗，章鱼哥——
,只有你和我在一起
.for hours and hours and hours
.几个小时、几个小时、几个小时
.And then the sun will come up
.然后太阳就会升起
.And it'll be tomorrow
.那就是明天
.And we'll still be working
.我们仍然会工作
Ahh, it'll be just
,like a sleepover
啊啊，就这样吧
,就像过夜一样
only we'll be sweaty
.and covered with grease
只有我们会出汗
.并涂有油脂
Are you ready to
?rock, Squidward
你准备好了吗
？摇滚，章鱼哥
.No-
。不-
Good, because-
.we've got customers
很好，因为——
.我们有客户
.Here-
。这里-
Please hit me as
.hard as you can
请打我为
.尽你所能
Psst, Squidward, I'm working in-
.the kitchen [LAUGHS] at night
嘘，章鱼哥，我正在工作——
.晚上的厨房[笑]
.Don't hold back-
.不要退缩-
?Hey, Squidward, guess what-
？嘿，章鱼哥，你猜怎么着——
.I'm chopping lettuce at night
.我晚上在切生菜
Look at me, I'm swabbing
.the bathroom at night
看我，我正在擦拭
.晚上的浴室
.Ow, I burned my hand at night
.哎呀，我晚上把手烫伤了
,Night, night, night, night
,night, night, night, night
，晚上，晚上，晚上，晚上
,night, night
,night, night, night
，晚上，晚上
，晚上，晚上，晚上
.nuh, nuh, nuh, nuh night
.nu​​h，nuh，nuh，nuh 夜晚
!Night
！夜晚
?Will you please-
？请你-
Here, give me a moment's
.peace and take out the trash
在这里，给我一点时间
.和平并倒垃圾
All right, taking-
.out the trash
好吧，拿——
.倒垃圾
.Taking out the trash at night
.晚上倒垃圾
?You mean outside
？你是说外面
That's where the-
.dumpster is, yes
那就是——
.dumpster 是，是的
.I don't know, Squidward-
.我不知道，章鱼哥-
.It's kind of dark out there
.外面有点黑
But I thought you-
.liked the night shift
但我以为你——
.喜欢夜班
.You're right-
。你说得对-
!For the Krusty Krab
!对于蟹堡王
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
.Piece of cake
.小菜一碟
?So you're not afraid-
？所以你不害怕-
.Pfft, nah-
.噗，呃-
Well, I am, especially-
.after-- [GULP] well, you know
嗯，我尤其是——
.after-- [咕噜咕噜] 好吧，你知道
?What-
？什么-
?What do I know
？我知道什么
?You don't remember-
？你不记得了-
.It was all over the news
.这件事上了新闻
.Tell me-
。告诉我-
.Tell me
。告诉我
No, no, no, I, I-
.probably shouldn't
不不不，我，我——
.可能不应该
It would ruin the
.night shift for you
它会毁掉
.为你上夜班
?What happened-
？发生了什么-
?What happened
？发生了什么
You mean you've-
never heard the story
你的意思是你已经-
没听过这个故事
?of the Hash Slinging Slasher
?哈希投掷杀手
?The Slash Bringing Hasher-
?斜线带来哈希-
?The Hash Slinging Slasher
?哈希投掷杀手
The Sash Ringing, the Trash-
,Singing, Mash Flinging
腰带响了，垃圾——
,唱歌, 捣碎投掷
,the Flash Springing, Ringing
.the, the Crash Dinging-- duh
、闪光弹跳、响铃
.the，崩溃叮当——废话
.Yes, the Hash Slinging Slasher-
.是的，哈希投掷杀手-
But most people just
!call him the Haa-- uah
但大多数人只是
！称他为哈——呃
Because that's
all they have time
因为那是
他们有时间
!to say before he gets them
！在他得到它们之前说
!Ahhh-
！啊啊——
.Tell me the story
.告诉我这个故事
Years ago, at this-
,very restaurant
许多年前，此时——
,非常餐厅
the Hash Slinging
Slasher used to be a fry
哈希吊索
Slasher 曾经是一个鱼苗
cook, just like
.you, only clumsier
做饭，就像
.你，只是笨手笨脚的
And then, one night, when he
was cutting the patties it
然后，有一天晚上，当他
正在切肉饼呢
.happened
.发生了
?He forgot the secret sauce-
？他忘记了秘方-
.No-
。不-
?He didn't wash his hands-
？他没有洗手-
.No-
。不-
.Irregular portions-
.不规则部分-
!No-
！不-
He cut off his own-
.hand by mistake
他切断了自己的——
.手误
?You mean like this-
?你的意思是这样-
?Or like this
？或者像这样
?Or this
？或者这个
?But what about this
？但是这个呢
?Or this
？或者这个
.Except he wasn't a sponge-
.除了他不是一块海绵-
?So-
？所以-
!So it didn't grow back-
！所以它没有长回来-
!Ahh-
！啊——
And he replaced his hand-
.with a rusty spatula
然后他换了手——
.用生锈的抹刀
.And then he got hit by a bus
.然后他被公共汽车撞了
,And at his funeral
.they fired him
,并在他的葬礼上
.他们解雇了他
?So now every-- what day is it
？现在每个--今天是星期几
.Tuesday-
。周二-
Tuesday night his ghost-
returns to the Krusty Krab
周二晚上他的鬼魂——
返回蟹堡王
.to wreak his horrible vengeance
.进行他可怕的复仇
!Oh-
！哦-
.But tonight's Tuesday night
.但是今晚是星期二晚上
.Then he'll be coming-
.然后他就会来-
?How will we know-
？我们怎么知道-
There are three-
signs that signal
有三个——
表示信号的标志
the approach of Hash
.Slinging Slasher
哈希方法
.投掷斩击者
First, the lights will
.flicker on and off
首先，灯光将
.闪烁开和关
.Next
。下一个
?Dude, can I have some ketchup-
？伙计，我可以喝点番茄酱吗-
.Oh, here you go-
.哦，给你-
Next, the phone will ring, and
.there will be nobody there
接下来，电话铃声响起，
.那里不会有人
And finally, the
Hash Slinging Slasher
最后，
哈希吊索砍杀者
arrives in the ghost of
.the bus that ran him over
到达的幽灵
.把他撞倒的公共汽车
Then he exits the bus
and crosses the street
然后他下了公交车
并过马路
,without looking both ways
!because he's already dead
,无需双向查看
！因为他已经死了
Then he taps on the window
.with his grizzly spatula hand
然后他敲了敲窗户
.用他那灰白的铲子手
.No-
。不-
.He opens the door-
.他打开门-
[CREAKS]
[嘎吱声]
He slowly approaches
!the (ECHOING) counter
他慢慢靠近
!（ECHOING）计数器
?And you know what he does next
？你知道他接下来会做什么
?What-
？什么-
?You really want to know-
？你真的想知道-
?What-
？什么-
?Are you sure you want to know-
？你确定你想知道吗-
?What-
？什么-
?What
？什么
?What does he do
？他做什么的
.He gets you-
.他明白你-
[SCREAMS]-
[尖叫声]-
[LAUGHS]-
[笑]-
[LAUGHTER AND SCREAMING]
[笑声和尖叫声]
.Oh, right-
.哦，对了-
.Heh hoo
.呵呵
[SCREAMS]-
[尖叫声]-
.SpongeBob-
.海绵宝宝-
[SCREAMS]-
[尖叫声]-
.SpongeBob, I was-
.海绵宝宝，我是-
[SCREAMS]-
[尖叫声]-
.I was just-
.我只是-
[SCREAMS]-
[尖叫声]-
.I was just-
.我只是-
[SCREAMS]-
[尖叫声]-
!SpongeBob, I was joking-
！海绵宝宝，我开玩笑的——
?What-
？什么-
.It's not true-
.这不是真的-
None of it's true
没有一个是真的
?It's not-
？它不是-
.Of course not-
.当然不是——
.Nobody has a spatula for a hand
.没有人手上有铲子
.It was all a joke
.这都是个笑话
.Oh-
。哦-
[LAUGHS]
[笑]
[HOOTING]
[倒彩]
[GHOSTLY MOANS]
[幽灵般的呻吟声]
[CREAKING]
[吱吱作响]
[PLOINKS]
[砰]
[SCRATCHING]
[抓挠]
[PLOINKS]
[砰]
[SCRATCHING]
[抓挠]
[PLOINKS]
[砰]
[SCRATCHING]
[抓挠]
[PLOINKS]
[砰]
[SCRATCHING]
[抓挠]
[PLOINKS]
[砰]
[SCRATCHING]
[抓挠]
?Isn't this great, Squidward-
？这不是很棒吗，章鱼哥-
!Ahh-
！啊——
There's never time to wash-
.the ceiling during the day
从来没有时间洗澡
.白天的天花板
!Gahh-
！嘎——
,Open 24 hours a day
.what a stupid idea
,全天24小时营业
.多么愚蠢的想法
Who wants a Krabby Patty
.at 3:00 in the morning
谁想要蟹肉饼
.凌晨 3:00
[ALARM]
[警报]
.Oh, boy, 3:00 AM-
.哦，天哪，凌晨 3:00-
.Just look at this place-
.看看这个地方-
.It's like a ghost town in here
.这里就像一座鬼城
.Very funny, SpongeBob
.非常有趣，海绵宝宝
?What-
？什么-
And the lights will flicker on-
.and off, just like the story
然后灯就会闪烁——
.然后，就像故事一样
.I get it
。我得到它
,Hey, Squidward-
how are you doing
，嘿，章鱼哥——
你好吗
?that without moving the switch
？无需移动开关
.I'm not doing it-
.我不会这么做-
,It must be the stupid
.faulty wiring in here
,一定是傻子
.此处接线错误
This place isn't built
.to run 24 hours a day
这个地方还没建
.一天24小时运行
[PHONE RINGING]
[电话铃声]
?What
？什么
?Hello
？你好
.Nice try, Squidward-
.不错的尝试，章鱼哥-
?Nice try what-
？很好尝试什么-
The phone well ring, and-
.there will be no one there
电话铃声响起，然后——
.那里不会有人
.Oh, you crack me up
.哦，你笑死我了
.SpongeBob I'm not doing this-
.海绵宝宝我不会这样做-
.Oh, oh, calm down, calm down
.哦哦，冷静点，冷静点
?All right, what was it
？好吧，那是什么
There was the lights
.and the phone
那里有灯
.和电话
[PHONE RINGING]
[电话铃声]
And the walls will
!ooze green slime
墙壁也会
！渗出绿色粘液
.Oh, wait, they always do that
.哦，等等，他们总是这样做
?But what was that third thing
？但是第三件事是什么？
I didn't know the-
.buses ran this late
我不知道-
.公交车这么晚了
.They don't-
.他们不-
Well, they're-
.dropping someone off
嗯，他们是——
.送某人下车
[SCREAMS]-
[尖叫声]-
The Sash Ringing, the, the Flash
!Singing, the Bash P-pinging
腰带铃声、闪光
!唱歌，Bash P-pinging
!The Hash Slinging Slasher-
!哈希投掷杀手-
[CRYING]
[哭泣]
.At last you understand-
.最后你明白了-
.We're doomed
.我们注定了
.No, that's not it-
.不，不是这样的——
I am just so touched that you
would go to trouble to dress up
我很感动你
会很麻烦地打扮
as a ghostly fry cook and stand
on the other side of the street
作为一个幽灵般的油炸厨师和站立者
在街道的另一边
.just to entertain me
.只是为了娱乐我
.You must really like me
.你一定很喜欢我
SpongeBob, there are two-
.problems with your theory
海绵宝宝，有两个——
.你的理论有问题
.One, I hate you
.一，我恨你
And two, how can that be me
?when I'm standing right here
第二，那怎么可能是我
？当我站在这里时
[SCREAMS]-
[尖叫声]-
TOGETHER) The Hash)-
!Slinger Slasher
一起）哈希）-
!投石斩击者
.Get away from me-
.离我远点-
!Oh, going to get me
！哦，要来找我
!Get away
！逃离
SpongeBob, no matter-
,what I've said
海绵宝宝，无论如何——
,我说过的话
.I've always sort of liked you
.我一直有点喜欢你
Squidward, I used your-
.clarinet to unclog my toilet
章鱼哥，我用了你的——
.单簧管疏通我的厕所
?Huh-
？哈-
!Get away-
！逃离-
!Get away
！逃离
.Get out of here
.离开这里
!You're not welcome here
！这里不欢迎你
?Can I have a job application-
？我可以申请一份工作吗-
.I brought my own spatula
.我带了自己的抹刀
I called earlier, but I hung
.up, because I was nervous
我之前打过电话，但挂断了
.up，因为我很紧张
?Do you have references-
？你有参考资料吗-
.Wait-
。等待-
If that was you on the phone
and you on the bus, then
如果打电话的是你
然后你在公交车上
.who was flickering the lights
.谁在闪烁灯光
!TOGETHER) Nosferatu)-
！一起）诺斯费拉图）-
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
,La da dee, stitch one-
.pearl two, da da dee do
，La da dee，缝一针——
.珍珠二号，da da dee do
.Da day dee da dee do
.Da Day dee da dee do
[What? [SNIFFS
?What's that smell
[什么？ [嗅嗅
？那是什么味道
!The register
!寄存器
!SNIFFS] $49.08]
!嗅嗅] $49.08]
!That's a penny short
！这真是太短了
[SOBBING]
[抽泣]
.Oh, no, not a penny-
.哦，不，一分钱都没有-
.Help, somebody help us
.救命，有人帮助我们
.It's just a penny, sir-
.这只是一分钱，先生-
.It doesn't matter
。没关系
!Doesn't matter-
！没关系-
It's money that makes
.the world go round, boy
钱是用来赚钱的
.世界运转，男孩
It's money that keeps
.your pants square
是钱能留住
.你的裤子是方形的
It's money that keeps
.Squidward in frilly soap
是钱能留住
.褶边肥皂中的章鱼哥
.SNIFFS] Lilac]-
.SNIFFS]丁香]-
It's money that paid for-
.all them renovations we did
这是钱所付出的——
.我们所做的所有装修
No, nothing in
all the seven seas
不，里面什么都没有
所有七大洋
could matter more, not even
.that scrumptious, curvy cutie
可能更重要，甚至不是
.那个美味、曲线优美的小可爱
.I see her, Mr. Krabs-
.我看到她了，蟹老板-
A Krabby Patty with
.cheese, the classic
蟹肉饼
.奶酪，经典
,Not the sandwich-
boy, the curvy cutie
,不是三明治-
男孩，曲线美人
.holding the sandwich
.拿着三明治
Hey, that's my driving-
.teacher, Mrs. Puff
嘿，这是我的驾驶-
.老师，帕芙女士
?Mrs. Puff-
？太太。噗-
.Oh, she's married
.哦，她结婚了
.Oh, no, Mr. Krabs-
.哦，不，蟹老板-
.She's single
.她单身
.Then what happened to Mr. Puff-
.然后Puff先生发生了什么-
She doesn't like
.to talk about it
她不喜欢
. 谈论它
Oh, what I wouldn't give to-
have a lass like that on me
哦，我不会给予的-
我身边有一个这样的女孩
.claw
。爪
.Hey, I know-
.嘿，我知道-
Why don't I take you
?over and introduce you
为什么我不带你
？介绍一下你
.No, no, no-
.不，不，不——
,I'm, I'm, I'm too old, boy
.too hard-shelled for love
，我，我，我太老了，孩子
.对于爱情来说外壳太坚硬
Besides, I ain't
.properly dressed
另外，我不是
.穿着得体
.Ah, come on, Mr-
.Krabs, you look great
.啊，来吧，先生-
.蟹蟹，你看起来棒极了
,FLIES BUZZING] You wait here]
.while I go break the ice
，苍蝇嗡嗡]你在这里等着]
.当我去打破僵局时
.SpongeBob, no, wait-
.海绵宝宝，不，等等-
.I'm too nervous
.我太紧张了
.Ooh
.哦
.Hi, Mrs. Puff-
.嗨，普芙夫人-
!Ahh-
！啊——
.Hit the breaks, SpongeBob
.海绵宝宝，快点休息吧
.Ah, watch the tree
.啊，看树
!Left
！左边
,Wait, Mrs. Puff-
.we're not driving
，等等，普芙夫人——
.我们没有开车
.Oho, I'm sorry, SpongeBob-
.哦哦，对不起，海绵宝宝-
.I didn't expect to see you here
.没想到会在这里见到你
.I work here, Mrs. Puff
.我在这里工作，帕芙女士
?Want to meet my boss
？想见见我的老板
.Well, I'm not-
.好吧，我不是-
.Don't move-
.别动-
.Ohh-
.哦-
Mrs. Puff, I'd like to-
.introduce you to mister
普芙女士，我想——
.把你介绍给先生
Mrs. Puff, I'd like to introduce
.you to my boss, Mr. Krabs
泡芙女士，我想介绍一下
.你给我的老板，蟹老板
.Uh, hello-
.呃，你好-
[RAPID PANTING]-
[急促的气喘吁吁]-
.Psst, Mr. Krabs, say hello-
.嘘，蟹老板，打个招呼吧-
.Gyah ooh ooh-
.Gyah 哦哦-
,No, no, Mr. Krabs-
.just say, hello
，不，不，蟹老板-
.只是说，你好
!Ell ahh oh-
！呃啊哦-
Hm, perhaps another-
.time would be
嗯，也许是另一个——
.时间将是
!No-
！不-
Wait, he's trying to-
.tell you something
等等，他正试图——
.告诉你一件事
.Mr. Krabs-
。先生。蟹蟹-
.Yaghy blagh boogu blah-
.I don't understand-
。我不明白-
.Wubby wub-
.Uh, don't bleeb eh oh blag
.呃，别哭了，呃，哦，布拉格
Oh, I think Mr. Krabs-
is saying that he'd
哦，我想蟹老板——
是说他会
.like to hit you with a rake
.喜欢用耙子打你
!Goodness-
！天哪-
!No-ooh-
！不-哦-
.Ming, blagh ooh yab dod it
.Try to guess your weight-
.试着猜猜你的体重-
!Well-
！出色地-
.Hah voor rah voor-
No, wait, he-
--wants to take you
不，等等，他——
——想带你走
.Gah bu bada ba-
.on a date-- -
.约会—— -
.Ooha-
.噢哈-
?Is that true, Mr. Krabs-
？是真的吗，蟹老板——
Do you want to
?take me on a date
你想要吗
？带我去约会
.Aye-
.耶-
?What do you say
？你怎么说
?What do I say-
？我该说什么-
LAUGHS] I say, you have a]
.way with words, Mr. Krabs
笑]我说，你有一个]
.蟹蟹先生，言辞得体
.I still got it-
.我还是明白了-
.Heh heh
.呵呵
SPONGEBOB: Ready for
?your date, Mr. Krabs
海绵宝宝：准备好了
?你的约会对象，蟹老板
KRABS: I'm always ready when
.it comes to dating, lad
蟹蟹：我随时准备着
.说到约会了，小伙子
?SPONGEBOB: Breath spray
?海绵宝宝：呼吸喷雾
.Check-
。查看-
?Lucky hanky-
？幸运手帕-
.Check-
。查看-
.Giant rusty anchor-
.巨大的生锈锚-
?Huh-
？哈-
?Anchor
？锚
I can't find me
!giant rusty anchor
我找不到我
！巨大的生锈锚
.LAUGHS] Relax, Mr]--
.Krabs, just a little joke
.笑]放松，先生]--
.蟹蟹，只是一个小玩笑
.Good luck with you know who
.祝你好运，知道是谁
?Who's that-
？那是谁-
.Mrs. Puff-
。太太。噗-
.Oh, yeah-
.哦，是的-
.Well, wish we luck, lad
.好吧，祝我们好运，小伙子
Oh, Mr. Krabs, this dinner-
.has been so wonderful
.已经如此美妙了
The coral was cooked
.to perfection
珊瑚被煮熟了
.至臻完美
Oho, I don't think I
.could eat another bite
哦哦，我不认为我
.可以再吃一口
Oh, I doubt that, my-
.little shrimp boat
哦，我怀疑，我的——
.小虾船
[LAUGHS]-
[笑]-
.You're spoiling me, Mr. Krabs
.蟹老板，你把我宠坏了
I mean, foot rubs
,between courses
我是说，搓脚
,课程之间
.caricatures, imported music
.漫画、进口音乐
Nothing's too good for-
.you, my prickly peach
没有什么是太好了-
.你，我的仙桃
Oh, what I'm trying to-
.tell you Mr. Krabs is
哦，我正在努力-
.告诉你蟹老板是
Uh, sir, your fancy-pantsy-
.limousine is here
呃，先生，你的花哨内裤-
.豪华轿车在这里
.Wonderful-
。精彩的-
Puffily-poo, your
.chariot awaits
蓬松便便，你的
.战车等待着
.Well-
。出色地-
[WHISTLES]-
[口哨声]-
!Ahh-
！啊——
You'll never have to walk-
.again, my little lobster bib
你永远不必步行-
.再说一遍，我的小龙虾围脖
.Ehhh, argh
.呃呃呃
.Your bill, sir-
.您的账单，先生-
?What-
？什么-
!100$
Well, this can't
!possibly be correct
嗯，这不能
！可能是正确的
.Oh, my mistake, sir-
.哦，我的错误，先生-
.Thank you for pointing that out
.谢谢你指出这一点
.This is your bill
.这是您的账单
[SCREAMS]
[尖叫声]
[SOBBING]
[抽泣]
.I don't understand, Mr. Krabs-
.我不明白，蟹老板-
How can you spend
.100,000 in one night$
你可以怎样花
.100,000 一晚$
Oh, SpongeBob, I couldn't-
help but spend every cent
哦，海绵宝宝，我不能-
帮助但花掉每一分钱
.I had on her
.我对她有
.I couldn't control myself
.我无法控制自己
?What are you going to do-
？你会怎样做-
.I don't know boy-
.我不知道男孩-
.I've got another date tomorrow
.明天我还有另一个约会
I'm caught in the middle of
.me two great loves, sweet Mrs
我被夹在中间
.我是两个伟大的爱人，亲爱的夫人
!Puff and the rest of me money
！泡芙和我剩下的钱
[CRYING]
[哭泣]
I wish there was-
.some way I could help
我希望有——
.我可以提供帮助
.Perhaps there is, boy-
.也许有，孩子-
I'm putting you in
.charge of me money
我把你放进去
.向我收取费用
.I don't get it, Mr. Krabs-
.我不明白，蟹老板-
You come with me on-
the date and don't
你跟我一起去——
日期和不
.let me spend any money
.让我花任何钱
Now remember, we keep it
.cheap by going to the park
现在记住，我们保留它
.去公园便宜
And no matter how
,much I ask you
而且无论怎样
，我问你很多
you don't give me
.any of me money
你不给我
.我的任何钱
.Now give me a dollar
.现在给我一美元
.Nope-
。没有-
.Good boy, you'll do fine-
.好孩子，你会做得很好-
?MRS. PUFF: Who is it
？太太。泡芙：是谁啊
It's me, my-
.beautiful bell buoy
是我，我的——
.美丽的钟浮标
[MRS. PUFF: [LAUGHS
.Just a minute
[太太。泡芙：[笑
.请等一下
!Flowers-
！花朵-
.Flowers, boy
.鲜花，男孩
.Go get flowers
.去买花吧
.But you said-
.但是你说-
SpongeBob, you can't-
call on a classy lady
海绵宝宝，你不能——
拜访一位优雅的女士
.like Mrs. Puff empty-handed
.就像泡芙夫人两手空空
We ain't talking
.about this or this
我们不说话
.关于这个或这个
.We're talking about this
.我们正在谈论这个
.MRS. PUFF: Almost ready
。太太。泡芙：快准备好了
.Hurry, boy, get the flowers-
.快点，男孩，去拿花-
Mrs. Puff, you're as
.beautiful as ever
泡芙女士，你就像
.一如既往的美丽
Aheh, that's funny, I thought-
.I heard SpongeBob's voice
啊啊，这很有趣，我想——
.我听到海绵宝宝的声音
.Uh, you did-
.呃，你做到了-
.He'll be right back
.他马上就回来
He's our personal
.assistant for the day
他是我们的私人
.当天助理
.Oh-
。哦-
E-excuse me, I have to
.call my insurance agent
E-对不起，我必须
.致电我的保险代理人
.Of course, my beautiful Puff-
.当然，我美丽的泡芙-
.Ahh haahh
.啊哈哈
Mr. Krabs, I got the-
.flowers you wanted me to buy
蟹老板先生，我得到了——
.你想让我买的花
?What's that-
？那是什么-
I got the flowers-
.for Mrs. Puff
我收到了花——
.献给泡芙夫人
.We had an agreement, boy-
.我们有一个协议，孩子-
You ain't supposed to
.spend any of me money
你不应该
.花我任何钱
.But you said-
.但是你说-
.MRS. PUFF: Here I come
。太太。泡芙：我来了
.For you, Mrs. Puff-
.为了你，普芙夫人-
.Oh, flowers-
.哦，鲜花-
.Oh, how thoughtful
.哦，多么周到啊
.And here's a box of chocolates-
.这是一盒巧克力-
SpongeBob, where's
.the chocolates
海绵宝宝，在哪里
.巧克力
Mr. Krabs, the budget-
.doesn't allow for
蟹老板先生，预算-
.不允许
SpongeBob, you can't-
go to Mrs. Puff's house
海绵宝宝，你不能——
去泡芙太太家
.without chocolates
.没有巧克力
!Hurry
！匆忙
I bought the-
.biggest box they had
我买了-
.他们拥有的最大的盒子
,Buy, buy, buy-
,spend, spend, spend
,买买买——
,花费,花费,花费
?is that all you can think about
？这就是你能想到的全部
.MRS. PUFF: Oh, Eugene
。太太。普夫：哦，尤金
Here's those chocolates-
.I bought for you
这是那些巧克力——
.我给你买的
?What do we do today, Mrs. Puff
？我们今天做什么，普夫夫人
Dinner, dancing, a
?trip to the moon
晚餐、跳舞、
？月球之旅
Psst, Mr. Krabs, we're just-
,going for a walk in the park
嘘，蟹老板，我们只是——
,去公园散步
?remember
？记住
Actually, a walk in-
.the park sounds perfect
其实，走进去——
.公园听起来很完美
.It's a beautiful day
.这是美好的一天
I'll just need to
.get a sun hat and
我只需要
.戴上遮阳帽并
Mrs. Puff needs a-
.sun hat, SpongeBob
帕夫夫人需要一个——
.太阳帽，海绵宝宝
.Well, I think she-
.嗯，我认为她-
The sun is beating down-
.on poor Mrs. Puff's head
太阳正在下山——
.在可怜的帕芙夫人的头上
As your financial-
.advisor, I suggest
作为您的财务 -
.顾问，我建议
There's no time-
.for suggestions
没时间了-
.寻求建议
!Go buy a hat
！去买帽子吧
.But-
。但-
.Today-
。今天-
.Don't worry, Mrs
.Puff, I'll shade you
.别担心，女士
.噗，我来遮荫你
!SpongeBob, hurry
！海绵宝宝，快点
.One shady hat-
.一顶遮阳帽-
.Good job, lad-
.干得好，小伙子-
.Oh, well, uh, thank you-
.哦，好吧，呃，谢谢-
.But you didn't need to buy one
.但你不需要买一个
.I have a hat in the closet
.我的衣柜里有一顶帽子
?Didn't need to buy one-
？不需要买一个-
?You hear that, boy
？你听到了，男孩
.We didn't need to buy a hat
.我们不需要买帽子
Aren't you supposed
?to be saving me money
你不是应该
？为我省钱
.I'm trying, Mr-
Krabs, but you keep
.我正在努力，先生-
螃蟹，但你保留
telling me to buy
.things for Mrs. Puff
告诉我要买
.泡芙夫人的东西
.It's all really confusing
.这一切真的很令人困惑
.SpongeBob, I'm sorry-
.海绵宝宝，对不起-
.This is my fault
.这是我的错
.I'm not thinking clearly
.我没有想清楚
,I'm making a sailor's promise
,boy, from this moment on
,我正在许下水手的诺言
孩子，从这一刻起
I won't ask you to buy
.anything for Mrs. Puff
我不会要求你买
.任何给泡芙夫人的东西
.NARRATOR: A few moments later
.旁白：几分钟后
SpongeBob, Mrs. Puff-
!needs a new fur coat
海绵宝宝、泡芙夫人-
！需要一件新毛皮大衣
[PANTING]-
[气喘吁吁]-
!You're spending all me money-
！你花光了我所有的钱-
.Puffy needs a new pair of shoes
.Puffy需要一双新鞋
[PANTING]-
[气喘吁吁]-
!You're breaking me, boy-
！你让我心碎了，孩子——
.She needs fine jewellery
.她需要精美的珠宝
[PANTING]-
[气喘吁吁]-
!KRABS: Not that fine
!KRABS: 不太好
.SpongeBob
.海绵宝宝
!SpongeBob
!海绵宝宝
.SpongeBob
.海绵宝宝
!SpongeBob
!海绵宝宝
.SpongeBob
.海绵宝宝
!SpongeBob
!海绵宝宝
!Bob
！鲍勃
!SpongeBob
!海绵宝宝
[PANTING]-
[气喘吁吁]-
SpongeBob, I'm-
.glad I caught you
海绵宝宝，我是——
.很高兴我抓住了你
.I want you to buy Mrs. Puff
.我要你买泡芙夫人
!Wait-
！等待-
.Don't tell me
.别告诉我
You want me to
run down the store
你要我
跑下商店
and buy Mrs. Puff
,something she doesn't need
并购买泡芙夫人
,她不需要的东西
then you want me to run back
,here so you can say, argh
然后你想让我跑回来
，在这里你可以说，啊
SpongeBob, you're
.spending all me money
海绵宝宝，你是
.花光我所有的钱
,And then I'll say
,but Mr. Krabs
,然后我会说
，但是蟹老板
!I'm only doing what you said
！我只是按照你说的做
Then you'll say, we're not
.talking about this or this
然后你会说，我们不是
.谈论这个或这个
!We're talking about this
！我们正在谈论这个
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
.But lad, this time's different-
.但是小伙子，这次不同了-
.Mrs. Puff needs this
。太太。泡芙需要这个
?Are we going to the park soon-
？我们很快就要去公园吗-
.Please, lad, I'm begging you-
.求你了，小伙子，我求你了-
I'm a lonely, old
.crustacean who's found love
我是一个孤独的老人
.甲壳类动物找到了爱情
.Don't let me lose her
.别让我失去她
[SOBBING]
[抽泣]
,Mr. Krabs, don't-
.don't cry, Mr. Krabs
，先生。螃蟹们，别——
.蟹老板，别哭
.Come on
。快点
.OK, I'm going to get it, see
.好吧，我去拿它，看看
Cheer up, Mr. Krabs, here's
.that washing machine you wanted
振作起来，蟹老板，这是
.你想要的那台洗衣机
?Cheer up-
？开心点-
How can I cheer up
when you're spending
我怎样才能振作起来
当你花钱的时候
!all me hard-earned cash
！都是我辛苦赚来的钱
.See, you just did it again-
.看，你又这么做了-
Lad, I can't help it if you're-
loose with other people's
小伙子，如果你是的话我也无能为力——
与他人的关系松散
.money
。钱
Do you think Mrs. Puff will need
?a dryer to go along with that
你认为普夫夫人需要吗
？与之配套的烘干机
Well, Mr. Krabs, do you-
?want to know what I think
好吧，蟹老板，你——
？想知道我的想法
[SHOUTING FAKE CURSE WORDS]
.Mr. Krabs
[喊着假脏话]
.先生。蟹蟹
[SHOUTING FAKE CURSE WORDS]
.wallet
[喊着假脏话]
.钱包
[SHOUTING FAKE CURSE WORDS]
.spend
[喊着假脏话]
.花费
[SHOUTING FAKE CURSE WORDS]
[喊着假脏话]
.Oh-
。哦-
:SPONGEBOB
[SHOUTING FAKE CURSE WORDS]
:海绵宝宝
[喊着假脏话]
!Mr. Krabs' wallet
[SHOUTING FAKE CURSE WORDS]
！先生。蟹蟹的钱包
[喊着假脏话]
I didn't know SpongeBob had-
.such a colourful vocabulary
我不知道海绵宝宝有——
.如此丰富多彩的词汇
Actually, there's something I'd
.like to say, too, Mr. Krabs
其实，有件事我想要
.蟹老板先生也想说
I'm afraid I just
don't feel comfortable
恐怕我只是
感觉不舒服
.accepting all these gifts
.接受所有这些礼物
I'd rather go Dutch
.if you don't mind
我宁愿去荷兰
.如果你不介意的话
.OK-
。好的-
You're a very sweet-
.man, Mr. Krabs
你是一个非常可爱的人-
.man，蟹老板先生
.Ooh-ahh-
.噢-啊-
[END THEME MUSIC]
[结束主题音乐]